(Leonard:)I'm sorry,
I should have mentioned this earlier.
(Howard:)My last name is Wolowitz.
(Christie:)Oh. That's so cool.
(Christie:)My first Jew.
(Sheldon:)I imagine there aren't
very many kosher cornhuskers.
- But you're still taking me shopping?
- Anything you want.
(Christie:)Okay, I'll go pack my stuff.
(Howard:)When they perfect human cloning,
I'm gonna order 12 of those.
(Leonard:)Howard, can't you see she's using you?
Who cares? Last night,
she pulled off her blouse and I wept.
Look, Howard, I know her, okay?
(Penny:)She'll have sex with anyone
as long as they keep buying her things.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(Howard:)Yay.
(Howard:)If you'll excuse me,
I have some bar mitzvah bonds to cash.